# ZAIN ALABDEEN KHARTABIL

Web Developer



# **ABOUT ME**

Creative and forward-thinking with history building cutting edge websites and applications with challenging demands and visions. with 2+ years of experience in developing and designing web applications and managing databases.

- 🔀 zainkhartabel1995@gmail.com
- +40 791 434 445
- linkedin.com/in/zain-alabdeenkhartabil-662019192
- Bucharest, Romania

# **LANGUAGES**

Arabic

English

Romanian

## **EDUCATION**

# **BSc in Information Technology Engineering (2021)**

**Damascus University** 

**Software & Information Systems Engineering** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Sham Innovation SRL**

Full Stack Web Developer 11/2020 - 12/2021 Bucharest, Romania

.Net Core & .Net 5 MSSQL Server & Entity Framework Blazor HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript , Bootstrap & Jquery

#### **Orbits Ideal Solutions**

Full Stack Web Developer 10/2019 - 10/2022 Damascus, Syria

.Net Framework & .Net Core MSSQL Server ,MySQL & Entity Framework HTML, CSS, Javascript , Bootstrap & Jquery

## **MY SKILLS**







CSS



Java Scrip



.Net



SQL



# **COURSES**

BIG DATA ANALYTICS: OPPORTUNITIES, CHALLENGES, AND THE FUTURE (3/2021)
Griffith University

## **VOLUNTEERING**

### IT Support (8/2015 - 12/2018)

**Damascus University** 

Maintenance of laboratories in the faculty of Information Technology Engineering

#### **HOBBIES**









Reading

Football

Swimming

Music